I'm a music lawyer.
Last year, we did $487,000.
The thing that's stopping me right now is qualified leads.
If you just need more leads,
it's gonna be one of two things.
The option one is you start running meta ads.
Option two is you just make more content.
And here's the beautiful part.
You can do both of those things
and they accomplish the same objective.
Do you have any kind of big accomplishment
that you've had happen?
Last year, we helped artists close over $5 million.
I would put that front and center,
included in every YouTube video that you have.
So when you introduce yourself to edify you,
that's gonna elevate the brand overall.
Yeah, we just need to make a shitload more content,
better content, and then run the best content as ads.